[
    {
        "question": "م ا ل ي و ي",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ي ا ن",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ف ي ل و",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ن ي ر ا",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ا س ا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر و ت ا م ه",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ا ي ف و ال",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ل و ن",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "ل ي ا ي ر",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي ا ز د",
        "response": "دازاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "و ل ا",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ا د ا م ا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ش ي ي ت و ر ي",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ش ي ت ا ت ي ا",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ب ي و ت",
        "response": "توبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ا ب ا و ن",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي ي ف ل",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ا ر ا ش ي ا ه",
        "response": "هاشيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت و ر و و ب",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "و ب س و ي",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي م ر",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "و ي س ي ش",
        "response": "شيسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي د ك",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "س ا ك ا م ي",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ز و ن ا د",
        "response": "دانزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن غ ي و",
        "response": "وينغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ن ي ه ن ش ي ت",
        "response": "تينشيهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ن ه و ك ي ب",
        "response": "بيكوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "ج ي ا ك ي ز ا ك",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ا ا ر ي ج",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه و ن و ش ي",
        "response": "هوشينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ي ك و ك و",
        "response": "كوكومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي و غ",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي و ش ت",
        "response": "تشيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ي و س ا س",
        "response": "ساسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "و ك و ز ي ن",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ا ر و د ي م",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ج ي ي ن",
        "response": "نيجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ا س ا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ز ا ي ل",
        "response": "ليزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ا غ و ا ك",
        "response": "كاغويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن ا ي ه",
        "response": "هينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ا و ا ل",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ا ن ا ي ه",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "س و ت ن ي ز",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك و غ و ن ي ر",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي ف ي ل",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ا ر و ك",
        "response": "كورتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ا و س ي ه",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
       "question": "و ن س ا",
        "response": "انوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا ن غ و ك ي ا ب",
        "response": "بياكوغان"
    },
    {
       "question": "ك و ش و",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ك و ي د",
        "response": "ديكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "م ي ا ي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ن س ج ا ن ا ف",
        "response": "فانجانس"
    },
    {
       "question": "و س ل ي ي و",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "غ و م و س و ت",
        "response": "تسوموغو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ي م ا ن ا ن",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ن ز ي ا",
        "response": "ايزن"
    },
    {
       "question": "ك ي ر ا ز ا",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ر ا ه ا ر ا و ا",
        "response": "اوراهارا"
    },
    {
       "question": "و ي ي ن ا",
        "response": "اينوي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا ن و ه غ",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
    {
       "question": "ي ن ل  ي ر ي ك",
        "response": "كيريلين"
    },
    {
       "question": "ر و س و ا ت ي ن ه",
        "response": "هيناتسورو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ي ل ش ت ي ر",
       "response": "ريتشيل"
}
      ]